<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<sentEmail>
    <body>Hello Lachgar,&#13;
&#13;
In the coming weeks, Google Play will launch new personalization options  &#13;
that give you more seamless control of your personalization preferences and  &#13;
allow you to better manage your data in Play.&#13;
&#13;
Personalization provides a richer experience in the Play store, helping you  &#13;
discover exciting games, useful apps, relevant offers and much more, all of  &#13;
which is tailored to you. Learn more about personalizing your Google Play  &#13;
Store experience  &#13;
&lt;https://notifications.google.com/g/p/ANiao5q0Db802CTlMK5oM2iRbX0fOBLBEjjyrDUzkEPXSNtyvkq41eV0TpL5P75Bvrxw1RQmI57j075ilULrp8kpzY6kPcEIqcu7GzZiEkTYndnbyx8uBRAj8aq31eSl0m945AO9NTvl84-7HdMPp0VhrrxoFTqEJOshIJ-5pSXTPBoXXPMpwAfzPdtD0W-l9PWCN8fgWcCshQ_0Yb1W8mHEe4dEMhT8MQWFARddu6JLYWyR5v9J58xtvygRRDDuqW_Iv6kKiULk_MhhDBcGiErINV6dWK54JHxJfm1gRRfiuqXIsnwwzO-wauJAFFyakSTDmHTunsP4neA&gt;&#13;
&#13;
Once available, these new features - alongside existing Play  &#13;
personalization controls - will be easily accessible by visiting  &#13;
Personalization in Play from the Google Play Store menu. This new  &#13;
destination will be a one-stop-shop for tailoring your personalization  &#13;
preferences in Play, giving you a more powerful way to:&#13;
&#13;
• Manage all of your personalization options on Google Play and easily view  &#13;
activity and access personalization controls&#13;
&#13;
• Choose which apps, books or other library items are used to personalize  &#13;
your Google Play experience. With one click you will be able to exclude use  &#13;
of Play data associated with that app for personalization in Play. Some  &#13;
examples of data that would be excluded for that app would include when you  &#13;
install or uninstall it, purchases that you make in it and your app  &#13;
activity. Learn more about new personalization options  &#13;
&lt;https://notifications.google.com/g/p/ANiao5rJVGcd7IEIPuUKfjyy_uPckBuY6jOW66g9Xf4YuWtBhQIv-JP5p2-fcVtk4YTrKul6I4pov2VWAf3YMst_Cl2fpIrDnZUzVnRsInewXxCYfr-eijAkwvDRiWFC52JXgpraS7Pl___r8s3K896aP5cAGBYzh91tZK_niJGMTJH-u0gL4iY9j7AArSgQk-4n1oZbDies6cAdJY1iZOgLaUL-jQ0Z8E4p0MroIOvRoxVrPaTM6WAWMJ8x2M1zjKLcygdfbfHL-Vhg3B5PkCg04QirzZuyTrPKAphTT0CMz1MbRADg&gt;&#13;
&#13;
With these enhanced controls you can ensure that you have a better Play  &#13;
experience that is personalized to you and continues to respect your  &#13;
privacy preferences.&#13;
&#13;
Should you have any questions please visit our Help Center  &#13;
&lt;https://notifications.google.com/g/p/ANiao5oQyWzlD0kmWxQZcYBqR35mPytRw_e3YLgl-q2LZytcD1bRq_5jn3dHWBCtmrOOrCBJ3pYOLl0m4eLOs1VBVxZg74nEtWuh2a_VT3eQwpHGDjWBiiaCTtEn7HuV_dJaWxP8PkzijYBqd1swC1ARXRQSCwasVhOM9BUEnd-Vj2_VJNRMeOeQBYupmkJpqLKJJqlE8oW1PI-Uyn6kARmlqKq3rtvJK7Lq_tOjz2nGBf-oqwhxgbes9-exmAtgwm9caA&gt;  &#13;
or get in touch  &#13;
&lt;https://notifications.google.com/g/p/ANiao5p9k2uraaeWTwNzscFjE8Ubpj-6vTSeSymAUzpd3U5F51Fq9hXNLNLsjCrRb_pgrRhBYNylrFeNzEUeaxrrtjkyUBKLHRz14yJh3Fz5inZ1TfBYtQvV3ktS4B4LrJXlEvRhbK5JRpsDhI0uTl6SDzegXQrGgNvyeJRGrkTwdPCLdPbxHnYcVWXPBgnrr-QHPSP1Y3mgkwmHkXqaVsicTPGOgavwkAXN9Zo3SWcDZMMwJQDB&gt;.&#13;
&#13;
Thank you for using Google Play!&#13;
&#13;
(c) 2024 Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA&#13;
&#13;
You have received this mandatory email service announcement to update you  &#13;
about important changes to your Play product or account.&#13;
&#13;
Please do not reply to this email, as we are unable to respond from this  &#13;
email address. If you need support, please visit the Google Play Help  &#13;
Center  &#13;
&lt;https://notifications.google.com/g/p/ANiao5pjW1w_t7S2xiaAHf11Vf7PHMsYVRbU-xOJeYswNqqOCS-AlcZ615CfXFnOBwuWPDv2hY13aSG2U7vHPEDAr7mPFMRsVRta-K5d49J3oCMyUBXMsbbocnC01zqng6cXlAGVLtdNkR6HZ-pUAV7qeN8d41f60du_5zriY8iBuHnq6XTWtMoa1fPz2K_OnOkmFjsNG9_X4t_Se7NnUtamWX6PJ7XcCb1mHOdHt2TWvlRS-GgKMdcdxJzB32vAyiSW6ttr3bkGrHrv_6o7yojk&gt;.</body>
    <recipients>Google Play &lt;googleplay-noreply@google.com&gt;</recipients>
    <sentDate>2025-05-18T21:23:27.656+01:00</sentDate>
    <subject>Re: New Options to Manage Personalization on Google Play</subject>
</sentEmail>
